http://www.3dinspection.com/en/about/privacy-policy.html

800 745 6126
HomeProducts3D Inspection SystemPremier EditionFocus SolutionsMobile Apps3D Comparison ChartSystem RequirementsProduct PurchaseTry 3D!Sales DemonstrationsCase StudiesTestimonialsFree Trial DownloadContactGeneral Contact InfoSales InquiriesContact Tech SupportLearning PortalAbout
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to 3D Inspection Systems. This statement describes 3D Inspection System’s privacy practices for its own Web site, as well as the Web sites 3D Inspection Systems hosts for its customers, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. This privacy statement does not disclose how 3D Inspection System’s customers use data collected on Web sites that 3D Inspection Systems hosts for them, or may link to.
Personal Information
You can visit www.3dinspection.com or any 3D Inspection Systems hosted Web site without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. However, to access certain portions of the Web site, you may have to submit information such as user-id and password, or to access some services we provide, you may have to give us personal information such as your name and address and e-mail.
To access our transaction programs, we may ask you for your address and/or credit card information. When registering via 3dinspection.com, we may also ask you to choose a security question to answer (such as your mother’s maiden name or your pet’s name). This required information is necessary for us to process transactions, issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against credit card fraud, and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account. Our hosted sites may contain surveys, and other forms for collecting information. 3D Inspection Systems often publishes aggregate results to such surveys on its Web site.
Parts of our site invite may you to subscribe to a newsletter, obtain more information or apply for a relationship with us through one of our partner programs such as our Affiliate or Marketplace programs.  The information that you voluntarily submit may be shared with our technology partners or our business alliance partners and others to provide you with more information. It is 3D Inspection Systems practice to provide an opportunity for any person to remove themselves from a 3D distribution list by sending us an email removal request.  If an email sent to you from 3dinspection.com has a link at the bottom that gives you an opportunity to unsubscribe, and you wish to unsubscribe from our list, then simply click on the “remove” or unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email and submit. Or you may request us directly to remove your email from future correspondence.  After opting out, you will not receive email from 3dinspection.com, unless you send an email to us, and we therefore reply.  Please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving future information about products or upgrades that may be available to you.
Information security and quality
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures, such as using industry accepted encryption for transmission of credit card information, to help keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete.  Some information concerning you may be stored on servers secured in our Fort Myers, Florida office. We take data security seriously and endeavor to protect this data. In addition to normal precautions such as physical security, firewalls, and intrusion detection software, we employ strict security policies and procedures that govern the management of both physical and logical infrastructure. These policies and practices, however, may not apply to information that is transferred offline, such as information we obtain from an Affiliate application submitted on paper.
Web site traffic information
When you arrive at or leave any 3D Inspection Systems hosted Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on our hosted site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our hosted sites. We use this information only in an effort to better understand visitor preferences and to manage the load on our servers.
Cookies
We sometimes use cookies to collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better service. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly.
Disclosure to third parties
We will only share personally identifiable information with a third party if and when the individual submitting this information has permitted us to do so, or if we are required by law to do so.
Other Sites and Business Partners
We provide links that take you to other web sites. We encourage you to review privacy and other policies at third party sites you visit, since we cannot insure those sites follow privacy policies.
Modifications
3D Inspection Systems may in the future alter or add to this Privacy Policy, especially as we add new services to our site. Accordingly, please check this part of our site from time to time to see if there has been a change.
General
These are our current internal guidelines, which we make you aware of as a convenience. This is not a contract.
Search
SEARCH
GO!
download buttons
View My Cart >>
Need Support
Poll
Your favorite 2019 platform for 3D Mobile?
iOS (iPhone/iPad)
Android
Windows
I prefer the desktop program
iOS (iPhone/iPad)
(191 Votes)
32.26%
Android
(237 Votes)
40.03%
Windows
(47 Votes)
7.94%
I prefer the desktop program
(117 Votes)
19.76%
Vote Now
View Result
Vote Form
Total votes: 592
603282733
[{"id":"21","title":"iOS (iPhone\/iPad)","votes":"191","type":"x","order":"1","pct":32.26,"resources":[]},{"id":"22","title":"Android","votes":"237","type":"x","order":"2","pct":40.03,"resources":[]},{"id":"23","title":"Windows","votes":"47","type":"x","order":"3","pct":7.94,"resources":[]},{"id":"24","title":"I prefer the desktop program","votes":"117","type":"x","order":"4","pct":19.76,"resources":[]}]
["#ff5b00","#4ac0f2","#b80028","#eef66c","#60bb22","#b96a9a","#62c2cc"]
sbar
200
200
/en/polls.html?id=6&task=poll.vote
MSG_ERROR_NO_SELECTION
Please select either existing option or enter your own, however not both.
MSG_THANK_YOU_NO_RESULTS
COM_COMMUNITYPOLLS_LABEL_ANSWERS
Votes
HomeProducts3D Inspection SystemPremier EditionFocus SolutionsMobile Apps3D Comparison ChartSystem RequirementsProduct PurchaseTry 3D!Sales DemonstrationsCase StudiesTestimonialsFree Trial DownloadContactGeneral Contact InfoSales InquiriesContact Tech SupportLearning PortalAbout
